Good morning.
I'm Leori.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm from Nagano Prefecture.
I lived in Matsumoto until I was 12 years old
Welcome back.
I'm here for the first time in 17 years or so.
You can see the Yarihata on the side of the tallest white mountain.
My parents told me that you can see the spear field only on a clear day.
I have an episode that my parents taught me that you can only see the Yarihata when the weather is good.
The ridge line is clearly visible today.
That's right.
It's so clear in the sky, isn't it?
Thank goodness the conditions are so good!
The weather was as if it was welcoming you, too.
Matsumoto Castle holds fond memories for you, doesn't it?
Yes, it is.
I was in a marching band in elementary school.
a world-class music festival that graced the summers in Matsumoto.
Leor was in charge of the trumpet
Maybe he was in this band.
That feeling of eating at a festival when you are a child
With Leol, an artist representing the Internet age
To my hometown Matsumoto
Eating, laughing and strolling around
We get to know the real face of Leol, which you don't usually get to see.
I reconfirmed that Matsumoto was a town that made my heart rich just by being there.
I was born in a very nice place.
First, let's go to that street where I used to go to have fun.
Here we are at Achi Street. Yes, this is my first time here. It was the first time I showed my face here. It's become my face. That's right.
A good old shopping street that has long been familiar to local residents. It's a memorable place for Leal.
Yeah, but I don't think it's changed at all.
This cotton candy making machine on both sides of the street makes me nostalgic.
I used to make cotton candy here.
I'm not sure if it's still working.
May I bring my camera?
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much! OK! Classic OK!
Oh, my God, this is so exciting.
Oh, my God, it smells so sweet.
Wow, this brings back memories!
You've come to the right place for this.
It's so soft and fluffy!
Amazing, isn't it?
Bon appétit!
It's so good.
It's just like the ones we used to eat at festivals when I was a kid.
It's true that cotton candy is hard to come by as an adult.
It's hard to eat cotton candy as an adult, isn't it?
You make it yourself. It's nice to be able to eat it.
I've been coming here since I was little, and I'll keep coming until I grow up.
There's a lot of them.
It's nice.
It's still here.
There it is.
That's great, I'm a little impressed.
Leol's five dishes are my favorite.
I went to the coffee shop recommended by Anna Otsuki.
There's a great place to fill up on a little bit of food.
I'd love to introduce it to you!
Here it is!
It's called Corollo Coffee.
Yes!
It's a relatively new store.
So it's definitely a first for you.
Yes, it's my first time.
Hello. - Hello.
I'm Leol.
It's a nice place, isn't it?
It's a nice atmosphere that makes you feel like you're going to be here for a long time.
Corollo Coffee, which opened in December 2021, is a popular coffee shop where you can enjoy carefully selected coffees from all over the world roasted in house.
The secret of the store's popularity is said to be its unusual serving method.
We would like to know what you recommend at the store.
Yes, it's very original.
You can choose the design and size of your favorite buckwheat chocolates.
Pour espresso and milk into it and make a latte-like drink.
Then you pour espresso and milk into it and make a latte-like drink.
I would recommend the menu which is competing with 10 other people.
Does the taste vary depending on the item?
Yes, if you choose a larger cup.
If you choose this larger cup, the milk content is higher than in coffee, so it gives a mellower impression.
If you choose this smaller cup, the amount of coffee is relatively larger.
You can feel the taste of coffee.
I like café au lait lately, so I'd like to serve it with a little more milk.
The second one from the right. No, thank you very much for this kappa.
It's very nice. It's fun to choose.
Yes, it's fun to choose.
We'll have each one with the chocolate of your choice.
The buckwheat chocolate with the coffee is fresh.
And the latte art is hard-shaped. It's adorable. - It's adorable.
I'll have one.
It's very milky. Mild, very mild.
And the coffee is fragrant and a little sour.
And you can even see it being made with such care.
The space itself is very cozy, so you can savor it slowly.
There is also a full food menu that goes well with the coffee. On Saturdays, Sundays, and holidays, the restaurant offers a monthly plate that uses locally grown ingredients.
Leor chose this waffle topped with bacon and a fried egg.
Mr. Leal is a surprisingly hearty eater, isn't he?
I'm going to eat it.
I feel like it's a waste.
What do you mean by "mottainai"?What is mottainai?
I don't know.
I don't want to miss this yolk.
I'm at the best part.
Bacon, eggs, and waffles all the way.
Anna Otsuki has avocado toast.
What a photogenic dish with avocado boldly placed on a piece of campagne.
You can't go wrong with this one.
It's the best! Sticky and rich!
The sauce in between is a little creamy.
Delicious! It goes well with coffee, too, this kind of meal.
Yes, it's so good!
Pairing with dried fruits, chocolates, and other sweets that go well with coffee is also popular!
We use specialty coffees.
We always have about 10 kinds of coffee on hand.
I try to bring out the best of the coffee's ingredients.
Because it is an agricultural product, it is in season at different times of the year.
I stock accordingly.
Two people with experience at a restaurant in Tokyo
Mr. Yukino's dream was to open his own restaurant in his hometown of Matsumoto.
Matsumoto was the first place that came up as a candidate for where to open a restaurant.
Aren't there many independent restaurants? Restaurants
I think Matsumoto is a good place for that.
Compared to Tokyo, it's better.
Raising one year old twins while running a business
The restaurant is also a place where the family can relax.
I'm busy raising my children every day, but I try to do something fun at least once a day.
I enjoy the harmony with my customers and my family.
I think I enjoy doing this every day.
The fact that we are so close to each other is one of the things that makes me glad that I opened the restaurant in Izumoto.
I think it's great that your parents run a coffee shop, and that you are children of such good roots.
Growing up in a nice aroma.
I've been drinking a little bit of all kinds of beans since I was a kid.
I'm sure they'll be able to tell the difference quickly.
Are you thinking of educating gifted children like that?
I'm thinking about it.
Corollo in Esperanto, an artificial language, means color.
I want to eliminate walls.
This is also common with Leol's musicality.
I try not to write lyrics that make people feel their gender or age.
When I was a child, I didn't want to feel pressured to do so because I was a girl.
I didn't want to be like that because I was a girl.
I feel that I share a lot of the same thoughts as you two.
In a sense, borderless is a central part of Leol's work.
Yes, I think that's a theme.
Youth is so much in the spotlight.
We tend to think of youth as something that is good because we are young, but it is something that everyone loses.
I think it's something that everyone loses, and everyone is leaving it behind, but there must be something to gain.
I'm sure everyone loses something, and everyone loses more and more, but there is something to gain, too, isn't there?
Like education, intelligence, and so on.
I wanted to sum up all those things and express them in one word.
That's why I wanted to sum it all up in one sentence, "Now is the youngest time.
When I listen to the song, I find myself humming along to it.
I'm glad.
I felt the same way.
I was dancing a little.
by H.
The next is a one-man store run by a man of my generation, and it's like the fashion haven of this city.
It's a sort of a temple for fashion in this city, a place where you can go if you like fashion, if you like clothes.
I'm here today to introduce you to a vintage clothing store called "Fance.
I've got a lot of colorful things I'm interested in, too.
I'm very pleased to meet you. You're very fashionable.
I'm embarrassed. Do you like vintage clothes?
I like that no two pieces of vintage clothing are alike.
We have some old stuff, but we also have some trendy items and some beautiful items.
We also have a selection of trendy, slightly beautiful and misshapen items.
These are men's shirts, right?
It's so cute.
The color is very nice.
The owner, Ms. Shikagawa, is from Matsumoto City.
After graduating from a fashion school in Tokyo, he made a U-turn and opened his own store.
How long has this store been in business?
Now, it's been 6 years.
And then you really just straddled the Corona as well.
That's right.
We were closed during the Corona period.
It's right in front of the station.
It was pitch-dark, and we were the only place with lights on.
There were no people walking around.
It was a difficult time for us.
With no clear future, we focused on online sales.
He realized something at that time.
After becoming Corona, the items that sold well were
like something you can wear at home or something easy to wear.
like something you can wear at home or something comfortable.
What do you mean by a change in demand?
It has changed so much.
Do you feel that the demand for music is changing as well?
It still depends on the venue.
I have to do live shows where I don't point the microphone at the audience.
I've thought a lot about the need to do live shows where I don't point the microphone at the audience.
I have thought about it a lot. How to do it.
Fast forward.
Wow!
Cute.
What's the theme?
The theme is "Tokyo Geidai Students.
It's like a Tokyo University of the Arts student, isn't it?
This jacket is the main piece of coordination.You've chosen this jacket as the main part of your outfit.
This one has a square neck.
I don't wear this often, so it's fresh.
Round glasses and a beret.
The shiny one-piece dress is a trendy yet original coordinate.
And Nico!
A little happy hand.
Do you talk a lot with your customers when they choose your clothes?
Yes, we start by talking about clothes.
We talk about all kinds of things.
I think we are very close to our customers.
It's really a homey atmosphere, and I'm completely at home here.
What kind of store do you want to make?
I want to keep doing what I'm doing because it's meaningful to keep doing it, and I want it to stay the same.
Corona, there are still some difficulties.
I want to do my best.
I really sympathize with the idea of continuing.
I'm sure that if you keep going, you'll be able to see what you want to see.
I'm sure that there will be a view that you can see after you keep going.
I hope I can get over the hard times I'm going through.
Let's work hard, not just as a hobby.
That's right.
We are the same age.
Leol's music originates from Matsumoto.
Like your experience in the marching band?
I think it's a lot.
I play a musical instrument, but it is more like a musical or show biz, and I was attracted to the idea of a comprehensive art form that combines not only music but also visual art,
I enjoy creating artwork in general, including how to create a world view in a live performance.
As a musician, do you have roots in Mr. Matsumoto?
I think so. Matsumoto is one thing, but also the marching bands I met in Matsumoto, and the castle town's unique high-colored atmosphere.
I think that kind of glamour is at the root of my music.
Are there any songs inspired by Matsumoto?
When I was a child, I participated in the Matsumoto Bonbon festival with my parents.
It is a summer festival of the people of Matsumoto.
I think that song is one of the most danceable and upper-range Bon Odori songs in Japan,
The recently released song "Aokiya Karatsu" is inspired by Matsumoto Bonbon.
I took a look back at the lyrics of "Matsumoto Bonbon" in about 2021,
I was thinking about the major breakups and the eye-baggers, and how there is also the excitement of encounters,
The song expresses in depth in one sentence that life is also about parting while there is also the excitement of meeting,
I thought it was a very good lyric, singing about something universal.
To a place Leor will never forget.
I'm visiting there for the first time in 17 years.
There's one last place I'd like to take you.
And that's this one.
This is the one I miss the most today.
Excuse me.
I miss the feeling of this restaurant.
Excuse me for interrupting.
I heard you won an award for marching.
You know, when you get a good score on a test.
When I got a good score in a test or something like that.
I used to be taken to this restaurant.
It was founded in 1973. A place where you can enjoy an affordable, authentic steak.
Here you go. Thank you. It brings back memories.
This is garlic.
My favorite is the filet steak with homemade garlic butter.
It's been 17 years since I've had a taste of home.
Bon appétit!
Super tasty! So delicious!
It's just as good as it was back then!
It brought back so many memories!
Bhajji is something you remember!
Have you changed the recipe since then?
No, we haven't.
It's been passed down from generation to generation.
What Mr. Otsuki ordered was a shell-in steak.
As the name suggests.
A scallop surrounded by tender meat.
Delicious!
This is what I call a synergistic effect!
The moment when the seafood flavor of the scallops and the flavor of the meat are combined
It is indeed the best!
How was it today?
I didn't get to see it as a child.
I can see many things that I had only a vague memory of.
I could see many things that I didn't see when I was a child, and I reconfirmed that it was a town that enriched my mind just by being there.
When I first moved to Tokyo, I couldn't help but want to get out of the city.
I had a slightly different view of "hometown" than I do now, but after 10 years of music activities in Tokyo, I realized that I had a lot of things to do.
After 10 years of performing music in Tokyo
But after 10 years of music in Tokyo, I feel differently now when I walk around the places I did back then.
For the final show of your first national tour in two years
I chose my hometown, Matsumoto, for the final show of the live tour.
I'd like to cherish this hometown, or rather, I'd like to work hard and never forget the joy I felt when I first encountered that music.